question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Nutella is produced by the German company Ferrero.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
                                      "question": "In the video game &quot;Splatoon&quot;, the playable characters were originally going to be rabbits instead of squids.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Codemasters is the developer of the Gran Turismo series.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
                                      "question": "In Until Dawn, both characters Sam and Mike cannot be killed under any means until the final chapter of the game.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
     "question": "Studio Ghibli is a Japanese animation studio responsible for the films &quot;Wolf Children&quot; and &quot;The Boy and the Beast&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Animals",
     "question": "Tigers have one colour of skin despite the stripey fur.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
                                      "question": "A pasodoble is a type of Italian pasta sauce.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "The Kerbol System (from Kerbal Space Program) includes a Saturn analogue.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
                                      "question": "The song &quot;Megalovania&quot; by Toby Fox made its third appearence in the 2015 RPG &quot;Undertale&quot;.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "Psychology is the science of behavior and mind.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Geography",
                                       "question": "The capital of the US State Ohio is the city of Chillicothe.",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "Water always boils at 100&deg;C, 212&deg;F, 373.15K, no matter where you are.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Board Games",
     "question": "When setting up a chess board, the king is placed on a square of his own color.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Politics",
     "question": "One of Barack Obama&#039;s United States presidential campaign slogan&#039;s was &quot;Yes We Can&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Television",
     "question": "In Battlestar Galactica (2004), Cylons were created by man as cybernetic workers and soldiers.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "Green Day&#039;s album &#039;American Idiot&#039; is considered a &quot;punk rock opera.&quot;",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Geography",
     "question": "Toronto is the capital city of the North American country of Canada.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "The Sniper&#039;s SMG in Team Fortress 2, was originally intended to be the Scout&#039;s primary weapon.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Geography",
     "question": "Vietnam is the only country in the world that starts with V. ", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
                                      "question": "In the game &quot;Subnautica&quot;, a &quot;Spadefish&quot; will attack you.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "&quot;Sonic the Hedgehog 2&quot; originally was going to have a time travel system.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Television",
     "question": "In AMC&#039;s &quot;The Walking Dead,&quot; the characters Rick, Carl, Daryl, Morgan, Carol and Maggie were introduced in Season 1.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "The first Maxis game to feature the fictional language &quot;Simlish&quot; was The Sims (2000).",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Mythology",
     "question": "In Greek mythology, Hera is the goddess of harvest.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science: Computers",
                                      "question": "MacOS is based on Linux.", "correct_answer": "False",
                                      "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]
